Premium payable on renewal and on subsequent continuation of Bajaj Allianz are subject to change with prior approval from IRDA. Policy may be cancelled by Us or on Our behalf at any time,
on grounds of mis-representation, fraud, non-disclosure of material facts or Your non-cooperation. A grace period of 30 days is permissible. Any claim incurred as a result of Accidental injury during the break period
will not be admissible under the policy. Sum Insured enhancement can be done at renewals. Bajajallianz. Company Limited, Yerawada, Pune - 411 006. There is possibility of withdrawal of this product at any
time in future with IRDA approval. Bajaj Allianz is a joint venture between Bajaj Finserv Limited and Allanz SE. Both enjoy a reputation of expertise, stability and strength. The above mentioned information is
only indicative in nature. The contributed to any pre-existing condition. nuclear fuel, or from any nuclear waste. Pregnancy, resulting childbirth, miscarriage, abortion, or complications part thereof being te. Loan Care is a unique
insurance policy designed by Us exclusively for the enemies, rebellion, revolution, insurrection, mutiny, military or usurped. We will not cover any period of unemployment if You are self-employed. Nuclear energy, radiation. between 18
years and 65 years. efikar! 8. EMI Payment Cover. P ersonal Accident Cover. Loan Care proposal is subject to a minimum of 1 year and a maximum of 3 years. We will not
be liable for any claim arising out of Personal Accident Cover for Death, then We will pay towards the actual cost of transporting remains. We will make a one time payment of `5,000/-
each towards the cost of Premium Rate for. Your unemployment if it follows a period of casual, temporary or 1.79%o 3.49%o 5.16%oeducation of upto 2 of Your dependent children. Loan Care proposal would
be calculated as per the following details:Policy Period. Depending on the Policy Period and Your occupation status, premium forDay of hospitalization for a maximum of 30 calendar days during the policy period. Unemployment
arises as a result of termination of service due to: If you are not satisfied with policy coverage, terms and conditions, criminal intent or misconduct. renewal will not be refused except on the
vehicle during motor racing or trial runs. Your unemployment if it arises as a result of You being on family leave or grounds of Your moral hazard. 15. Your unemployment if it arises
directly or indirectly from war, revolution, admissible under the policy. 15. The eak period will not be used for military exercises or war games or. Actual engagement with the enemy, whether foreign or
domestic.